...has gotta be easier to deal with
than him touching her with it.
There's no junk-jiggling. We just talk.
(Howard:)Are you insane? With high-speed
Internet, you have at your fingertips...
(Howard:)...the greatest advancement in the field
of sex since the invention of the washcloth.
(Leonard:)I can't do that.
Heh, well, if you don't,
you're gonna lose Priya...
(Howard:)...to some fancy guy in a turban...
(Howard:)...who grew up
with Kama Sutra coloring books.
(Raj:)How can you be so racist?
(Howard:)Oh, come on, tell me I'm wrong.
(Sheldon(entering):)Oh, Leonard, good, there you are.
(Sheldon(entering):)I need you to check my head
for chair lice.
(Leonard:)I did it last night,
I'm not doing it again.
(Howard:)Just his head, right?
I don't wanna talk about it.
(Leonard:)You didn't catch bugs
from Penny's chair.
(Sheldon:)Yes, I did. And now they're cavorting
at the base of my hair follicles...
(Sheldon:)...like dancing hippies
at the Redwood National Forest.